Ah the
AHA
ah
ah ah ah ah ah.
ah Ah. ah Ah ah ah ah.
Ah ah
you're
the boss what's the boss.
The old. Agreement about
about. The battle it's
a slaughter. I mean didn't have
a chance and then you hear me it's just
people who don't understand we planned
a surprise attack to win and yet we were
the ones surprised a man walked into
a deliberate trap the Germans knew
what objective and as the lot exactly.
Well I got a call
a quarter. A
general speaking this is Captain Stuart
twenty eight division. And attack has been
repulsed along the entire sector. I have
to report a complete failure sending
a report. Captain Stuart reported that
the twenty eighth was beaten back to the
Germans must have known of our plans
before our own junior officers have to
know everything that's done here all
our orders and I thought our line of campaign
unknown immediately to the enemy for
the last year every time one of our plans
was miscarried it's been blamed on. Well
he must be caught but we're not exactly
certain what he looks like but we do expect
some results very soon and then till then
we are supposed to let the Germans go on
learning anything and everything they please
if you permit me. He's the best spy we
have but he's the keystone of our whole
system in Germany we can't afford to bring
him back we must bring him back it's well
known that strand is working in this
vicinity obviously we still
need to just operate as
a catching Williams is the man for the job.
Williams immediately and then Chandra's
instruct commander Phelps to have
a pilot stand by because
Williamson behind the German like
a good. Bennett.
Williams will be waiting for you at the
north edge of the words outside the model
nine o'clock he'll be wearing
a white smock so that you can identify
him from the air under Yes. Thank you
Cheerio bells. Back to headquarters.
A jolly fine announcer trouble are you
sure you want to do it then of course
moccasin all that you know. Already put
all the blood on tomorrow if one of the
rebel tracks episode of valley of the put
you about the morality nine o'clock I
thought.
The
the. Exact
spell. And.
Notify their service that we have
work tomorrow done well. Over.
Well whole.
Already.
Well
old
girl.
Has. Told
a world that's right a science fair been
a pretty good chance in the world
where you're going to probably. Have.
The you. Go.
Along the bullet
hole the old
Little.
Old. Old the world. The.
Only cure the litter box proved by the.
City council interest.
Please don't go away. I
just. Want to show.
I want you to come back. Why.
I kind of. High school. You know. I think
I'm falling in love with. Him too.
I don't follow. A barrel.
I think. And I go
fishing for your past service to the
Fatherland and because of the success of your
mission at the English base hospital that
money is Imperial Majesty has ordered me
to confer upon you this declaration
this my following is the
most distinguished. And. You have
studied these directions this text
repeats that I will proceed to kill every
part of the commander submarine you can
do three he will conduct me to the north I
wish coast from there I will make my way
to Liverpool to Henry Thompson to take
care of the London and good backup that.
Despite the directions. He says that this
is actually the only terms those highly
esteemed by the British officials we
should have no difficulty No I was any
suspicion in placing on the I saw Benetton
and then it was anything Oh no certainly
not extensive It's just that you start
only with the name of the new cabinet
minister all along and you will take your
orders directly or indirectly whichever
you may choose on front standby
strand on and question is this No
just that I thought that it was in front
stainless along has been for several
months but this would give an entire army
corps to capture them and all the pilots
on the So Ho knobs constantly
communicating with us by while it was
a book. I feel very proud to have their
on I'm honored to be chosen to represent.
Excellency what is my objective in this
mission objective is to deliver desk blow
to the allies say from stand
that's all any of us know as
a new password or bail him out or follow
him out of it always following the answer
Naeem out sort of the most never
backward victory must be ours
but one object to win the war even
after we have to fight the fire.
No nation or group of nations can stop our
advance bands of German culture we are
destined to conquer the world
our case mistaken fungus
a NEW LEADER Well I. May not
live to see it some day.
Well.
The energy depleted you are
placing in the Venice.
Breaking very heavily. Was
a very difficult assignment no one suspects
means slightest. How did you convince
the Bennetts and I should be in there
by telling them the very sad story of
Francisco. Father
a terrible hardships and I don't mazing
escape from those German brutes. By the
time I finished I had all been on
the verge of tears. For myself.
By thinking. Now in the Bennett home in
addition to Mr and Mrs Bennett there's
a brother George the daughter
Dorothy wasn't wasn't.
Frank I think his name is but he's
in France on Air Force. There in
a moment. Well
I do hope you'll be happy I'm
sure I will. Just wait what.
We've Miss Hawtrey and Mr Thompson to see
Mr Bennett but of course this isn't about
was it please to come.
Think. You want expect I miss
you. So I thought I heard your
voice Mr Bennett George my present response
is what you do we'd be expecting you
about will you tell Mrs Bennett that our
guests are right at once Mrs Chumley going
to the library. I want
to sit down this country
to dance Thanks West so bad to
rediscover us who can be very happy
thank you I understand you had quite
a time to germinate Joe It's all right
really I don't mind talking about I think
this is wonderfully kind of you Bennett not
at all as I told you Miss watering her
father were interned in Germany from the
very beginning of the war and they were
treated like cattle was the bad really
until my father was accused of being an
English spy isn't bother to say how or
what he could have spied upon we condemned
him to death anyway July fourteenth eight
o'clock in the morning so my father
dragged in this hell and.
This is Miss France is for free Miss
Hawtrey I want to welcome my dear. And
our daughter Dorothy I'm very
happy to know you will be
a welcome addition to our family I'll have
nothing sent up to our room right away
although still at the Savoy You see I
couldn't convince Mr Hawtrey that you were
really welcome but I'm sure she understands
now don't you. Do that out on.
We relied on this hawk to slug ages at the
Savoy see that it's propaganda that was
for the. Peace Not me I think.
We'll have live for coffee and Mr
Bennett just about the. Only I could.
Fight with.
Now the case is going to tragic. But then
it was cheap the civilian got back into
bullets in his leg from the job. His wife
and baby were but at the borders I. Got
engaged heard about about this case asked
me to help him by giving him this job.
I've never regretted. Rat
and. That's certainly
a fine bunch of fellows had
to want. For German gun.
They would be the No. My dear you're quite
exhausted let be take you to your room.
It's been on great times and
I shan't see you again no
but I shall write to let you know how
things are going in America good luck thank
you. Goodbye because it is well I must run
along my trunks on pictures in the boat
train leaves at seven when I have
a good trip Thompson thank you I
shall good luck to you both thanks
a lot welcome to most
poetry fine men don't.
I don't my For example I take so not.
Bad with children. I have very
happy she stayed. Something out
of some sandwich but nothing to.
The you brought out maybe badly
for. Me to believe was telling me
that you too are
a victim of German cruelty. And I can quote
If tied to my country my wife my baby
or. Certainly have every right to feel
bitter but don't you think that there might
be people in Germany who feel equally bitter
toward the allies. We do not kill him
in
a baby. No but the Germans might
feel that anything once victory. So
we don't. Have only to push the bell
at the stake. I will call that one.
Oh. And if we remember always
to push the envelope with
a forward motion will be more easy it is
somewhat stuck please to remember always
all. Over forward to
do things with weapons
that. Are sort of the vilest. But we
sell but UPS aside experience with
a bell that works some of the work
rule never any and. Never backed.
Well
a bundle of you and you Counselor the
other parent who had told me. The
weather on cool told you not to show
sympathy for families who think that we're
just out here right even when we talk
like they always I mean. With someone you
want not to be Act passed on
our. Right to tell me I was.
The. One man made from strength
that I cannot and. Where
is it. I do not know it trust no
one by orders I received about
a part said another transmitter
strike. I'm so anxious to meet
a kid missing. The symbol of blind.
Or complete happiness. As
those whole country numb.
It can you or me or do you.
I mean. I think about.
Your I expect I was here to
live that. You know it's right
on time these are all been
checked. That I put them in
a safe. Frankly you pick them up in the
morning taken to the water is about
certainly going to be eight. M.M.
.
All these materials get across
the chest safely without
a hitch. Saw close to any other munitions
people I know said that to get
a concentration to take any chances.
He met with. The
heel of my shoe to be loose I
wanted to do both but this.
Didn't come with my duties. You
would visit it in at least twice
a week. And his secretary Mr East. Cuts
adult clothes patrol information
I don't work with. You have
a million books kind of
a graphical. Next time it rocks.
People and it's up it's. Going case it is
not empty it's restored because of the
information of the case of the typewriter.
Every eight years of the petitions and it
just. Sits in the library should. I think
that they go and do that with the service
a piece of looking. Forward. To the
old.
Little girl some of the
stuff that they use
a little I'm going to give up the stuff
in Japan and they're going to have
a little more right I'll be around again
tomorrow has all I'm going to give today
but often said. We have one
called Extra today or I took
a. Risk while I'm still
in the right which is
often the still there any further information
about the mother's offensive so. We.
Must know the exact location of the mother's
mission that's. Like I think that for
you tonight will.
I think some people say
oh. I want to get the.
Part don't I need help I ask for it to
come back up style. To go back for.
The.
Old.
Good evening with the best. Of the.
But yeah what are you doing down goes
down. I came out three books. I couldn't
sleep I just can't realize it but I'm free
I understand but you better upset when
you catch. A sweetheart I just can't.
Must trust you be yourself again
in
a few days about much of. The coming
. Years. What is it. Who's.
This I am exhausted I feel right now new
school shots come along I say what's.
That is this
a really it's don't know what. The
.
Evening Governor Good evening this
is. Nice night I'm squeamish here is
a better night. We're going to get no.
Moon.
But it's night and have a copy of
the latest English band come off
a generation dope. The earth the earth.
The girl. The
world the in.
The right gonna get hot
that's never going to see
a lot of its editorial wanted to ban
the ads have consequences not just
love the British porn was. The drawn
out ops edition step might be
just right we're going to get out.
With
the.
Whole of. The.
Afternoon. We're having And
yes he is and it's been
a busy Mrs Mr George is missing now and
then this gentleman has an appointment has
either a moment why did you wait
a moment I'll see if we can squeeze you in
you'll find the latest magazines on the
table and. They understand it's.
Often papers and Miss Hawtrey is
outside asked Would you please yes.
That's. True let's look. If you believe
that it will one person survived among the
seven hundred forty aboard be completed
steamship Victoria was dispelled today
authorities hold a surprise to be
on top you know without warning by
a German submarine This
would account I don't know.
What. He told me before he boarded the
Victoria that he didn't feel right about the
trip England's lost
a good man and THOMPSON
So they say George W.
Never struck you as being
a very big. You know I should say comfortable
but certainly not rich so he appeared
to me his box show him to have been invented
the wealthy Oh well mostly acquired
within the past twelve months
he wouldn't say that's.
His drug of its role. Interesting here
oh yes yes Mr Bennett looking into that
matter. Was an hour ago. And cuts of
the army and
a message relayed immediately and he got
thousand that he gets word. About that.
Hello hello humans are trapped there well
thank you Major biology you later I hope
so. I'm so sorry to have kept you waiting
that's all right Mr Bennett I've had an
interesting time reading
excuse me. And you stand
a while longer to crack it's been here for
some time is important I was shopping
near here and I thought I'd stop and say
hello I think at home all right. Bye bye.
Come inside Thank you. I
thanked. Them together
with the help.
Also. This fury that never cried.
But you'll excuse my office being in this
condition cracking but I'm told now by
five it's not practice no try to get out
of the week seven. You know something
I just picked up. A lot of X.'s
I just need it's
a code message that's the reason I stumble
over the wastebasket expressed in you
mean she's a too many to but
that's the best I can I think such
a thing just now she was transmitting
a message in the Wolf good code to her
diabetic the German intelligence was the
only one using it just
who else was in the office. All of us hope.
You remember when I dropped in to see
you were leaving the week as Miss Hawtrey
was also in the office of that time I
thought I called the end of
a code message that now I'm sure. Risen
to it tell me cry. I realize we can't
arrest either of them while there's any
chance of them needing strength is all
this leading us any closer to strength or
have you any news of him at all positive
proof that he should learn how long he's
been here of course we don't.
Yes what you want please.
Get Yes. Because of course immediately by.
The Bush people the six months
to come over there right.
I think we've hit on something breaks in
the ethics about man on the audience chap
named good. How do you find out what was
written Mr Bennett secretary she conveyed
the information to be for free through
a coded message on the typewriter.
To financially overlooks what to do
Love from this man cuts complete confirmation
you were right about Henry Thompson
he was the paymaster the spy ring got all
his money from Germany and Miss Hawtrey
Well we'll find out tonight whether he's
actually leading us anyway. You want to of
your men will be at the front door
of Mr Bennett's home but about
a given signal will be admitted I've been
about to tell you what to do they are
likely going to arrest to make. You
understand your end of things but since then
you intend placing Miss Hawtrey under
arrest but that depends entirely upon what
happened I'm afraid I don't quite understand
first I'm going to arrest her then
you'll know I do if Thompson hadn't gone
down with the Victoria we might have been
able to clear things up. This Thompson's
not that he didn't even sail on the
Victoria. That Brixton here was coming
to the twenty departure purely as
a matter of routine. He saw Thompson bought
the best right enough but he also saw
him leaving the pier after the vessel
and sailed that's when we began our
investigation. Thompson is
still in England times.
Yes. He was sent for
me but. I sent for you. At. Sea
with one of his aides thirty
you're depriving that's all. Right.
Under that lead of mind work out splendid
We picked up that man this afternoon he's
been back now and information. Where he
never heard of this fog nonsense like I'm
certain they've been in touch. That
won't be necessary I'm satisfied as
a German agent can see it's something about
every one of those dogs because from
the way it's time to take how important
is cards to us only in so far as it helps
us dogs trained the same for this part
that's right France translates and then
we've got to catch it stranded or I'll
guarantee to round up every German agent
this side of the western front
within a week it's taken
a long time but I think we're finally
closing in we get stranger so we've got to
catch him. In the meantime the
matters of equal importance to
a race. Tomorrow night the cabinet holds
a meeting secretly in Mr Bennett's. My
memory got the outside I expect you to keep
a close watch and understand
perfectly That's all thank you
all. You all the meeting
in the library yes.
You watched. The signal to get in at
nine thirty exactly come with me.
I got having straight yes can do exactly
as I said when I get the don't get the
signal stop at committee. The first.
I'm going to have
the
power the great.
The I'm.
The that's.
The place please help me what you want to
follow haven't hired me to ask me they're
going to kill me listen this is who are
these courts court you know you've got me
going the Master told you there isn't
any time to lose please I meet
a friend who stranded. Francis over the
dog. On. The back of transit.
Yes just
a moment. If you could. The
and open the door quickly.
Really why go I'm coming.
This is not going to get there
but if you come in here I pull
a man name because the Germans. Escaped
while being transferred to the town. I
heard
a lot of shooting and whistles. Is that
all. I believe it was an awful wreck
. Side of this Jewish cultural.
Terminate it was the British
intelligence. Yes I think the journalist
assistance in the car. Park. When I catch
someone he stays caught.
In. The case. I can
stomach this in the first place
somebody was accused of being
a trainer and explain everything about
I don't conceal and seemed so genuine.
You could have saved me if I'm going they
would have never found me thank you Alan
cried. You know his heart rate it's always
best to report such cases of ones I know.
Thank you for your cooperation for
that. I'm terribly sorry
I mean both. Could not.
You people that was interested.
To know you have never seen him.
Mean to the one thing that they have no
way to dogs or they would not set these
traps interesting. I thought you know
we've. Had two toddlers in the state
model not. By British cap and
a copy of the secret being translated
They never asked me how we learned
from strength. Since. The
children back home that
was.
I still don't think we've failed completely.
At that meeting. We'll make certain
that. I rather expect an
air raid at the same time.
The police.
The the. I you follow
me with you I just want to go
back to the outside want to have
a lot of my own. Time
. I've been hiding three days
I just had to come here one.
Was injured I've been under the privilege
of everything you've done that will be
reported to Scotland Yard. I hope I'll do.
What I tell you he was what he says but
it's optimum he's working with the English.
It's not impossible I know it to be
true only tonight he told me standard time
a place I don't care what he told you with
those in terrible danger of going. And
getting out I want you to come with. I can't
there's nothing to be gained here you
have no ties not
a body let's go together somewhere.
Where there's no war. I prefer.
And I noticed it took to tell
me. Why can't. People look to
the Middle East what good is work such
as ours when it leads only to death. The
journey to Germany I'm sick of experience
how many millions of people are being
killed in the past for those words how many
millions more must die the book of one
man's potential but the almighty some of
you may post of my country white people.
Saw it happening know it will
happen again. It's good to.
See you come. And sit inside make.
I want you to come with me.
Good luck. This is fine.
It's.
The poor.
I know that might want to write their
sister might make it bad to five hundred
twelve accept that it is happening.
When something as you you
told me to that's. That's
a three days ago. Is that I I
was delayed but I'm going now.
Down to where. Already Germany of course.
So I think I'd better see the
two girls. Maybe it's a D.
a Good idea if we let you
guess. That's. Something
that it could. Pick up their bags friend.
Without saying it again oh yeah that's
a rather than a prologue you can have
a period of time.
We're missing
a couple I can show that one fellow if
you're the kind of talk about his I Have My
last two years apart or mature
so. Who would you be. May I
ask who is to shoot a bad oh I live here
a little living listen to your face and
thank them it should be factual I'm sorry
and it's. What is everybody up steps X.
. I love reading oh
friend my dog I'm probably.
How are you. If you
overlook
a couple of ribs I left in France her dad
that I got to feel right when I have your
OK. However you have never better good what
are you doing in England Well our whole
squadron was older though we hear
this morning on the dump more than
a hundred planes called back most of us
on together my stand. Straight none of us
knows the least oh by the way I've gotta
call the war on them each day you'll let
us know what they say I will mother.
I went on I'm full I'll do. Your work as
a major address because. I'm
a generous benefiting. For
all I've Southend But
yes thank you for. What.
I say you must see Miss Hawtry were gone
mother of about you I'm Frank Bennett I'm
also glad to know you thank you. I have
seen you before no I don't think so I
think I have been to miss what you were
to field hospital in the morning and
federalists taken Mother
tell me Gus came from
a German intelligence camp but that's
correct Look here do you mind very much
telling me the truth you already know
my history. You are now my Francis for
treason I am
a lawyer. You seem to do everything else
why don't you tell me your name is Helen
that I do know you will the girl list the
backflipping after I cracked up the trunk
has not I tried to trace you I heard you
been captured the German advance can make
you complete liar out of me don't you call
that if you like but I can't understand
after what you did in the morning. Let's
remember the last time I saw you when I
was able to speak for the first
time. I tell you I'm sick no.
Really I wish you'd stop you are Helen.
Yes. I I didn't know that Monday I
knew it wait. Till just also for
another day and it's contagious. I think
it over to soon as they leave the hospital
. Not the soldier and the snows. Of
invasive and I. When you thought I was
a steep you kissed me you remember. When
you went to sleep I tried to call you back
I couldn't raise my voice above
a whisper that the vernacular in
the ME is. Telling. What are you
doing here.
I'm very secret service agent even your
father why I can't see anything you want to
leave me out.
Of the bottle not with you know
but not on top of the ASCO you.
To me but. You are here for the beating
a years old sod this way or. I
don't read the bit out.
Well that the last of them all be
this devalue the as. Keeping track of
a girl and we. Should it would
be better to arrest. Me two
more hours and I know all I
could be to know. What it is
already so that's just what we go inside
it's Francis price will you want to bet it
must see you but he was going back to the
logs about an hour ago I could understand
that.
Have you anything to tell me. Now nothing
new is developed. You are sure of.
The. Area about that means
in five minutes all electric
power will be shut off. Instantly to. US
then and. That was not the
last. Thing maybe you
had better come.
About if you only could if you only
arranged I will have. To turn right out.
Go dive into the sub I'd advise
you to make notes. If you're
playing.
Polo.
And now might be
a fine line for Nokia who are.
My congratulations. I might
have known you were British agent all
the time I asked questions Who are you.
Elaine Barlow of year
seven is possible I see.
Ready to meet Bennett boy. I've nothing
to hide you in the library when you told
him you remember being the Secret Service.
What would you have me do. Tell him
I'm a German spy Mr Bell. Takes. On
a frantic phone quite. I suppose
supposed to copy all right you
know what it means nothing. In
a trap every German agent in England one
by one. But there were places just as
wrecked. From stand there I'll see to
that and you'll never take him up not to
include. The Anybody. Have
you anything else that. If
you are still in doubt.
On. My deepest regret.
Prince Trent is wrong
he admits. You must transplant
exact. They have cited are sceptical
the of.
The of.
What he could do in the parks in the three
MINUTES IS US and British cabinet to
destroy the planned spring offensive. Will
be on their way across the league exist
now as I mentioned you
just told me talk with
a few strands of that.
Family trying to get away.
With the culture of.
The bomb on the table
quite where they go on
a full view of the room.
The cover of an excuse
about age and we have
a couple of on gospel. The
coping sense must be still here in the
God critter that was at the ground.
And goes behind.
The sign of.
The of.
The new.
As I see the of the generators.
The old.
Getting along famously
of it just plain. He's
a fine boy and Helen she is a
remarkable go I wish I know more about
a couple stuff. Of
a far more comfortable. So I had to give.
Her the strength of the prize at the way
it had to be no one else knew. And I gave
the assignment I don't know the playing
a part because of course. There are
occasions under the stolen pens when the
customers had. The time until the night
we set the bogus track by Helen. And we
almost overplayed upon trying to be too.
But it worked out alright in the end we
had to get strained and weak. But tell
me the sacrifices we are all making
you think they will eventually mean
something to mankind I wish I were able to
answer that question we want to help
humanity we fight was only because we crave
peace. And we pray that each was to be
the last. But always in the strange
scheme of things done maniac of
a lust for power. And then one moment
destroys the peace and tranquility we've
created through the years.
We hate. We just I see it
when we walk come we must
and will fight. And.